swapdom.com 2015-06-07

# Swapdom Privacy Policy

## Swapdom Inc.

Last updated: February 11, 2014

This Privacy Policy outlines the types of information that we collect about you through this website (the "Site") or through our item exchange platform made available on this Site (the "Service"), as well as how we use such information, the means by which we maintain it, and the choices you have about the information. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully.

Note that by accessing this Site or the Service, you accept the practices and terms set forth in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site or the Service.

## What information is collected from our users and how is it used?

The following describes the types of personal and other information we may collect about you, and how we use and maintain that information:

 **Registration.** Before you can utilize the Service, we will ask that you set up an account (your "Account Profile") by providing to us directly, or to us through a third-party platform (such as Facebook or Twitter, through its login functionality), certain information about yourself, such as your email address, username or other contact information, and to establish a password for your account. We will use this information for identification purposes, to communicate with you regarding your Account Profile, and to facilitate the functioning of the Service. Before you post items on the Service or select items for swapping, you will be prompted to add your first and last name and zip code to your Account Profile. We may keep all of this information indefinitely.

 **Swap Transactions.** When you engage in a swap through the Service, you will be asked to provide certain additional information necessary to facilitate the transaction, such as your full name, mailing address, phone number and PayPal account information. Your PayPal account information will only be maintained as long as necessary to complete your authorized payment, but we may keep indefinitely all of the other information collected about you in connection with a swap transaction.

 **Social Networking Offerings.** The Service is connected to certain third-party social networking offerings (such as Facebook, Twitter, and the like) that you may use along with the Service. We may receive information about you that you provide to such services (such as your account information). We may also receive information about you from these third-party services: (i) when you choose to post or otherwise share information on such services, or (ii) when other users post or otherwise share information about you on these services. We may use such information about you in a variety of ways, including to facilitate the Service. We may keep all of this information indefinitely. Note also that any such information that you or others post to any of these third-party services will be readily accessible by any other users of such service, subject to their terms of service and privacy policies.

 **Correspondence.** If you correspond with us via email, we may gather in a file specific to you the information that you submit. We may keep this information indefinitely.

 **Promotions.** We will collect information you give us when you register or you participate in any promotion sponsored by Swapdom, such as a sweepstakes or contest. You will typically be asked to provide your name, email address, and mailing address to participate in a Swapdom promotion. We store this information in our database and will use it to communicate with you about the promotion. We may also use this information to promote the Service to you in the future, unless you inform us that you opt out from receiving such communications.

 **URL and IP addresses.** Like many other websites, we collect information about our users’ utilization and navigation of the Site and the Service. This information helps us to design the Site and the Service to better suit our users’ needs. For example, the Site will track the URL that you visited before you came to the Site, the URL to which you next go and your Internet Protocol (IP) address. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer the Site and the Service. Your IP address also is used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information.

 **Cookies and Similar Technologies.** Like most websites, we also use cookies and similar technologies in connection with the Site and the Service. These technologies make using the Internet easier. For example, a cookie lets our Service remember that you are a registered user, which allows us to speed up your activities on the Service, and which allows you to enter your registration information less frequently while utilizing the Service. We may also use cookies or similar technologies to deliver content tailored to your interests. Such technologies may enable us to relate your use of the Service to personally identifying information that you previously submitted, such as calling you by name when you return to the Service. If your browser is set to reject cookies, or if your browser notifies you that you are about to receive a cookie and you reject it, then your use of the Site or the Service may not be as efficient or as enjoyable as it would be if the cookie were enabled. The information that we collect with cookies allows us to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze usage of the Site or the Service, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize the content, layout and offerings on the Site or the Service. We only use information collected with cookies on an aggregated basis without the use of any information that personally identifies you.

 **Blog.** Any information that you post to the blog on the Site, including personal information about you, may be disclosed and available to all users who have access to the blog, and thus is no longer private. Please keep this in mind when considering what to post and make publicly available through our blog.

 **Sending Messages to Other Users.** The Site includes functionality that enables you to send messages to other users through the Site (via your username). Any information that you send in a message to another user through the Site, including personal information about you, will be disclosed and available to such user, and thus is no longer private. Please keep this in mind when considering what to communicate to other users through our messaging functionality.

 **Third-Party Integrated Services.** We may implement certain third-party advertising or other content on the Service, or integrate other third-party offerings in the Service, enabling such third parties to collect information about you through your use of the Service. Any information collected through such integrated technologies is collected directly by these third parties for use by such third parties, subject to their own privacy practices and policies.

## To whom do we disclose information about you that we collect through the Service?

We may disclose both the personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information that we collect about you through the Site and the Service when we have your permission or in any of the following situations:

  * When you engage in a swap through the Service, your name and address will be displayed on the shipping label affixed to the package shipped to the user receiving your item, as well as on the shipping label provided to the user shipping his or her item to you. Accordingly, your name and mailing address will be viewable by the two other users involved in your swap (or the one other user in the rare circumstances where your swap is just a two-way transaction).
  * We may disclose information that we collect about you to our affiliates, and to third-party contractors who perform services for Swapdom in connection with the Site and/or the Service or to complete or confirm a transaction that you conduct with us. 
  * As noted, information about you collected by third-party services integrated with the Site or the Service will be disclosed to such third parties.
  * We may disclose the results of aggregated data about you and other users without restriction. In these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to personally identify you.
  * We may disclose information about you as part of a merger, acquisition or other sale or transfer of all or substantially all of Swapdom’s assets or business. We do not guarantee that any entity receiving such information in connection with one of these transactions will comply with all terms of this policy.
  * We may be legally obligated to disclose information about you to the government or to third parties under certain circumstances, such as in connection with alleged illegal activity in connection with the Site or the Service or to respond to a subpoena, court order or other legal process. We reserve the right to release information that we collect to law enforcement or other government officials, as we, in our sole and absolute discretion, deem necessary or appropriate.
  * We may also disclose information about you to third parties if needed to enforce our Terms of Service, including to investigate potential violations thereof; to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of the Service, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

If you use the Site or the Service outside of the United States, information that we collect about you will be transferred to servers inside the United States and maintained indefinitely, which may involve the transfer of information out of countries located in the European Economic Area. By allowing Swapdom to collect information about you, you consent to such transfer and processing of your data.

## What security measures do we employ for the Service?

To help protect the privacy of data we collect through the Service, where personally identifiable information is requested, we use technology designed to encrypt any information that you input before it is sent to us. In addition, we take commercially reasonable steps to protect user data generally that we collect against unauthorized access. However, you should keep in mind that the Site and the Service are run on software, hardware and networks, any component of which may, from time to time, require maintenance or experience problems or breaches of security beyond our control.

Please also be aware that despite our best intentions and the guidelines outlined in this Privacy Policy, no data transmission over the Internet or encryption method can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

## How can you correct, update or make choices about the information that we collect about you?

You may correct or update information that we collect about you by logging onto the Service and managing your Account Profile.

For our records, we may retain original and updated information for reasons such as technical constraints, dispute resolution, compliance with laws, fraud prevention, troubleshooting and agreement enforcement. In addition, we are not responsible for updating or removing any information about you collected through the Site or the Service already disclosed to third parties who have been provided information as described in this Privacy Policy.

Swapdom does not currently support "Do Not Track" preferences which can be selected through your browser. For more information about Do Not Track, visit donottrack.us.

## What are the policies of linked websites and other third parties?

This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information collected from you by Swapdom through this Site or the Service. You should be aware that when you are using the Site or the Service, you may be directed to other websites that are beyond our control or be interfacing with third-party integrated services. We would expect most, if not all, of these third parties will collect information about you when you use their offerings. However, Swapdom is not responsible for the privacy practices of third parties, regardless whether they are linked or otherwise connected to this Site or the Service. We encourage you to read the posted privacy policy whenever interacting with any third-party website or other offering.

## How will I know about changes to this Privacy Policy?

We reserve the right to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Please visit this page periodically so that you will be apprised of any changes.

## What is our policy on children users of the Service?

The Site and the Service are not directed to persons under 13 years old, and we do not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information from persons under 13. If we learn that any personally identifiable information of a person under 13 years old has been collected, we will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. If you are a parent or guardian and discover that your child under the age of 13 has obtained an account with us, then you may alert Swapdom at the address below and request that we delete that child’s personal information from our systems.

## What law governs your use of the Service?

By choosing to use the Site or the Service or otherwise provide information to Swapdom, you agree that any dispute over privacy or the terms contained in this Privacy Policy will be governed by the law of the State of California. You also agree to abide by any limitation on damages contained in our Terms of Service or other agreement that we have with you.

## How can you contact us?

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or need to reach us for any other reason, you may contact us by e-mail at info@swapdom.com.
